Why speaking out, like pulling teeth from my mouth
The devil's got my tongue, they're bringing out the pitchfog
Saying I locked your cars, locked your song, well
Let's throw up out of trucks and vows, fuck too soon and I'm losing the crowd
Drush your tight and tongue, I'm biting over and over again
No true when I say what I say, low-key like a brick to the face
Over-sharing, over-bearing, under-performing it fast
Ooh, ooh, ooh, am I ever gonna open my mouth again?
No, no, no
Ooh, ooh, ooh, how am I ever gonna open my mouth again?
Why just keepin' it down, feel like I'm pissed in a cage
Formin' at the mouth, pickin' a lock on the malls
All I got to keep me locked in a cycle and desperate to change
Now I throw up out of trucks and vows, fuck too soon and I'm losing the crowd
Drush your tight and tongue, I'm biting over and over again
No true when I say what I say, low-key like a brick to the face
Over-sharing, over-bearing, under-performing it fast
Ooh, ooh, how am I ever gonna open my mouth again?
No, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, ooh, ooh, how am I ever going open my mouth again?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, are we gonna open my mouth again?
We'll be right back.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.